Bob Bullock Comptroller of Public Accounts papers, Inclusive: 1970-1991, Bulk: 1975-1990
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Issues, 1971-1991; 2
  - General, 1979-1991; 2
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Hopkins, Michael H., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 8)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Horn, Jack J., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 9)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — House, Tammy, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 10)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Houseman, Gisela L., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 11)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Houy, Clifford W., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 12)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Howard, Sha, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 13)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Howell, Janie, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 14)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Howell, William R., 1988-1989 (Box 268, Folder 15)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Hubenak, Hon. Joe A., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 16)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Hudson, Sherry C., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 17)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Huff, Debra, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 18)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Huffman, Jerry W., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 19)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Huggins, Joseph H., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 20)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Hughes, David, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 21)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Hughes, Vester T., Jr., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 22)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Hunt, Donna, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 23)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Hurley, Alfred F., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 24)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Hutchins, David W., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 25)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Hutson, DeDe, 1989-1990 (Box 268, Folder 26)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Hutton, Robin R., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 27)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Ilgen, Kathy, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 28)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Inks, James M., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 29)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Irvin, John W., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 30)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Isaac, G. A., 1991 (Box 268, Folder 31)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Jackson, John W., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 32)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Jackson, Hon. Paul, Jr., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 33)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Janssen, Carolyn, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 34)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Johnson, Hon. Eddie Bernice, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 35)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Johnson, Glenda, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 36)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Johnson, Joan C., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 37)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Johnson, Laurie, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 38)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Johnson, Lisa, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 39)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Johnson, M. Tom, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 40)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Johnson, Suzanne, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 41)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Johnson, Thomas L., Sr., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 42)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Johnson, Virginia, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 43)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Johnson, Walter E., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 44)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Jonas, W. James, III, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 45)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Jones, Hon. Arves E., Sr., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 46)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Jones, Billie H., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 47)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Jones, David N., 1989 (Box 268, Folder 48)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Jovanovich, William, 1988 (Box 268, Folder 49)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Junell, R. Frank, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 50)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kamasaki, Alan, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kelleher, Herbert D., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Keller, Gary, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kelley-Mungle, Donna, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kelsay, R. E., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kent, Paula, 1988 (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kerr, David L., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kestenbaum, Richard, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kim, In T., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 9)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — King, Henry L., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 10)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — King, Karen, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 11)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — King, Phyllis, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 12)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — King, Susan E., 1990 (Box 269, Folder 13)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — King, Thomas S., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 14)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kinghorn, Janice H., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 15)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kirby, Rhonda C., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 16)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kirchner, Carole, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 17)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kirk, Clayton, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 18)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Klitch, Richard H., Sr., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 19)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Knight, Bertha, 1990 (Box 269, Folder 20)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kopecky, Hon. Leo, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 21)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kredloff, Mark, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 22)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Krier, Hon. Cynthia T., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 23)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Krier, Joseph R., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 24)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kucera, Gerald, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 25)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Kuehn, Claire R., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 26)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Laine, Cathy S., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 27)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Lancaster, Sally R., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 28)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Lanier, Susan, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 29)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Laurel, Melissa, 1990 (Box 269, Folder 30)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Lawless, Robert W., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 31)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Leal, Elizabeth, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 32)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Leggett, Hon. Judy, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 33)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Lemond, Xavier C., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 34)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Lemmons, Hon. Miriam E., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 35)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Lesch, James R., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 36)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Lewis, Tom, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 37)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Littlefield, Kenneth W., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 38)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Lowell, Dawn E., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 39)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Lucas, Bettye J., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 40)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Luce, Thomas W., III, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 41)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Luedecke, William H., III, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 42)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Lum, Albert B., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 43)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Lynaugh, James A., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 44)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Malnassy, Virginia B., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 45)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Malouf, John B., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 46)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Marbut, Robert G., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 47)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Marsalis, Noel D., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 48)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Marse, John, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 49)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Martin, Gary C., 1989 (Box 269, Folder 50)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Martin, Joyce K., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Martinez, Dave, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Massey, LuAnn, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Masters, Ben, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mastrocola, Frank, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 5)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Matthews, Mary Ruth, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mauldin, Melissa, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 7)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Maxey, Peggy, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 8)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Maxwell, Norris K., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 9)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mayes, Mike, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 10)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McBeath, Hon. W. Sherman, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 11)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McCarthy, Michael M., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 12)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McClellan, Michael T., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 13)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McClure, Weldon, 1990 (Box 270, Folder 14)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McCombs, Hon. Billy J., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 15)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McCue, Gwen H., 1990 (Box 270, Folder 16)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McCuller, Patsy, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 17)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McCullough, Leslie, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 18)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McDaniel, Carol, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 19)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McDonnell, John F., 1988 (Box 270, Folder 20)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McDonnell, Latrell, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 21)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McKinsey, Bill, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 22)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — McMullen, Hon. Dean, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 23)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Meacham, Gem, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 24)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Means, Noble, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 25)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mechaley, Gloria J., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 26)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Medley, Wendy, 1990 (Box 270, Folder 27)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Meincke, William A., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 28)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Merbler, Hon. H. J., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 29)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Merkens, Hon. Guido A., Sr., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 30)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Messbarger, Richard, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 31)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Metcalf, Jo Ann H., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 32)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mihatsch, Joe A., Jr., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 33)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mikush, Wanda, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 34)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Miles, Bruce R., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 35)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Miller, Hon. Frank R., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 36)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Miller, Jim, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 37)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Miller, Mark M., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 38)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mills, Philip, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 39)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Milner, Larry S., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 40)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Minick, Pam, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 41)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mino, Dennis, 1990 (Box 270, Folder 42)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mitchel, Jeffrey S., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 43)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mitchell, Richard A., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 44)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mitchell, William G., 1990 (Box 270, Folder 45)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mitchell, Hon. William R., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 46)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mobley, Richard L., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 47)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mobley, William H., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 48)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mokry, Bill, 1989 (Box 270, Folder 49)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Monteiro, Jose C., 1989 (Box 270, Folder 50)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Moore, D. Lewis, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Moore, John, 1990 (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Moore, Samuel L., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Morris, Jerry D., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Moss, Lloyd E., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Mudry, Joe, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Muffeny, Ann B., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 7)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Muir, J. Duncan, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Muller, John, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 9)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Murphy, Rick, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 10)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Murray, Colette M., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 11)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Murray, Erwin L., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 12)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Myers, J. Marc, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 13)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Nabers, Hon. Mary Scott, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 14)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Nash, Jeffrey L., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 15)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Naugle, Mary, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 16)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Nelson, Mark, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 17)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Nelson, Shirley A., 1991 (Box 271, Folder 18)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Newhouse, Bright K., Jr., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 19)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Newman, Brenda J., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 20)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Newport, Sherry, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 21)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Newsom, Bill, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 22)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Nolan, Clancy, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 23)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Norris, John, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 24)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Norris, Kathy, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 25)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Norris, Mike, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 26)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Norwood, Pam, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 27)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Notzon, Al J., III, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 28)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — O’Rear, Billie M., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 29)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Ormsby, Justin R., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 30)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Orr, Bobette K., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 31)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Orr, Joella, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 32)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Overshown, Pam, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 33)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Page, Jo, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 34)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Palmer, Nancy, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 35)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Paquette, Stella, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 36)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Park, Hon. Carolyn, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 37)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Parker, Esther Lee, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 38)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Parker, Robert F., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 39)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Patrick, Hon. Kae T., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 40)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Pattillo, Leslee, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 41)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Pawel, Tom E., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 42)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Peniston, Rita, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 43)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Penn, Lucyle, 1989 (Box 271, Folder 44)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Perron, Leo F., Jr., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 45)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Perry, Karen A., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 46)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Perry, Pat A., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 47)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Peterson, Mary P., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 48)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Petty, Dan S., 1989-1990 (Box 271, Folder 49)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Pfaffenberger, Roger C., 1989 (Box 271, Folder 50)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Phelps, Ed, Jr., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Phillips, G. Till, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Pickett, Ellen, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Pickett, Neal Y., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 4)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Pickle, Hon. J.J., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Piller, H., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Piner, Patsy, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Pitzer, Benny F., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 8)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Plotkin, Elaine S., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 9)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Plunkett, Brandi, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 10)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Poe, D. L., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Polk, Elizabeth, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 12)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Pope, Charley R., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 13)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Pope, Michael W., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 14)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Powell, Pattie, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 15)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Powers, Fran, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 16)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Prickette, John F., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 17)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Purdom, Paula, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 18)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Ramos, Fabio D., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 19)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Ratliff, A. J., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 20)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Reagan, Harold E., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 21)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Reece, Will, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 22)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Reese, Carla J., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 23)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Reeves, Nan L., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 24)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Rehm, Frieder, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 25)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Reidy, Patricia, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 26)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Renfro, William J., 1989 (Box 272, Folder 27)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Reyna, Maria Elena, 1989 (Box 272, Folder 28)
    - Publications: “It’s Texas, Here’s Why”: Correspondence — Reynolds, Debra, 1990 (Box 272, Folder 29)